[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 18, "question": "ORGAN: How do you feel about the punishment in terms of the fact the whole town now will have to football, do you think it is an appropriate measure to have been taken?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "How", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "the", "punishment", "in", "terms", "of", "the", "fact", "the", "whole", "town", "now", "will", "have", "to", "football", ",", "do", "you", "think", "it", "is", "an", "appropriate", "measure", "to", "have", "been", "taken", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 19, "answer": "I think it is inappropriate measure, I feel horrible for, you know, kids that are not involved, what I mean -- we are a small town, I mean things like shouldn't happen in a small community like ours.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "is", "inappropriate", "measure", ",", "I", "feel", "horrible", "for", ",", "you", "know", ",", "kids", "that", "are", "not", "involved", ",", "what", "I", "mean", "--", "we", "are", "a", "small", "town", ",", "I", "mean", "things", "like", "should", "n't", "happen", "in", "a", "small", "community", "like", "ours", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 30, "question": "What kind of thing has been going on?", "question_tokens": ["What", "kind", "of", "thing", "has", "been", "going", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 31, "answer": "He's cleats were taken out of his locker, water were put on them and they were put in the trash.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "cleats", "were", "taken", "out", "of", "his", "locker", ",", "water", "were", "put", "on", "them", "and", "they", "were", "put", "in", "the", "trash", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 33, "question": "And Anthony Phillips, has he been subjected to other racist abuse?", "question_tokens": ["And", "Anthony", "Phillips", ",", "has", "he", "been", "subjected", "to", "other", "racist", "abuse", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "VBN", "TO", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 34, "answer": "What's that, I'm sorry.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "'s", "that", ",", "I", "'m", "sorry", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Anthony Phillips"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "RB", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "NNS", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 35, "question": "I'm sorry, yes, I was just asking you, if he been subjected to other racist abuse, other than the graffiti?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'m", "sorry", ",", "yes", ",", "I", "was", "just", "asking", "you", ",", "if", "he", "been", "subjected", "to", "other", "racist", "abuse", ",", "other", "than", "the", "graffiti", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBN", "VBN", "TO", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "No, no this was the first incident that ever that word has been used towards my son.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", "this", "was", "the", "first", "incident", "that", "ever", "that", "word", "has", "been", "used", "towards", "my", "son", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "I made the point that, you know, if you're going to have rap stars and other leading figures in the black community using that word in songs and everything else, what kind of message does that send to the youth of America?", "question_tokens": ["I", "made", "the", "point", "that", ",", "you", "know", ",", "if", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "have", "rap", "stars", "and", "other", "leading", "figures", "in", "the", "black", "community", "using", "that", "word", "in", "songs", "and", "everything", "else", ",", "what", "kind", "of", "message", "does", "that", "send", "to", "the", "youth", "of", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "Well, I mean, what people fail to say to each other, I mean I guess that's, you know, that's your right.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "what", "people", "fail", "to", "say", "to", "each", "other", ",", "I", "mean", "I", "guess", "that", "'s", ",", "you", "know", ",", "that", "'s", "your", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 50, "question": "And Andrea, do you think that Isaac knows who sprayed this graffiti?", "question_tokens": ["And", "Andrea", ",", "do", "you", "think", "that", "Isaac", "knows", "who", "sprayed", "this", "graffiti", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "WP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 51, "answer": "No, he does not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "he", "does", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Andrea", "Isaac"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "What is your opinion?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "opinion", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "I don't think it's labeling them as quitters at all by doing that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "it", "'s", "labeling", "them", "as", "quitters", "at", "all", "by", "doing", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "Does he just want it get it sorted as quickly as possible?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "he", "just", "want", "it", "get", "it", "sorted", "as", "quickly", "as", "possible", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "Well, yes, you know, that, you know, he would be -- I mean that he would love to be playing.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "yes", ",", "you", "know", ",", "that", ",", "you", "know", ",", "he", "would", "be", "--", "I", "mean", "that", "he", "would", "love", "to", "be", "playing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 124, "question": "Why was A-Rod so uptight about everything?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "was", "A-Rod", "so", "uptight", "about", "everything", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "JJ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 125, "answer": "Uptight is not the word.", "answer_tokens": ["Uptight", "is", "not", "the", "word", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "Does he like you?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "he", "like", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "He hates my guts.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "hates", "my", "guts", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 144, "question": "Why there's so many think that he's just another Lance Armstrong in the making?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "there", "'s", "so", "many", "think", "that", "he", "'s", "just", "another", "Lance", "Armstrong", "in", "the", "making", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 145, "answer": "Well, honestly, I have no idea.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "honestly", ",", "I", "have", "no", "idea", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lance Armstrong"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alex", "Alex"]}, "docId": "131120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "CD", "CC", "NNP", "NNS", "CD", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "Are you simply enraged by what you view as (inaudible)?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "simply", "enraged", "by", "what", "you", "view", "as", "(", "inaudible", ")", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "There's not a human being with a brain that has a motivation to go against Alex that thinks everyone else gets 50 and Alex gets 211 and that's normal.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "not", "a", "human", "being", "with", "a", "brain", "that", "has", "a", "motivation", "to", "go", "against", "Alex", "that", "thinks", "everyone", "else", "gets", "50", "and", "Alex", "gets", "211", "and", "that", "'s", "normal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alex"]}, "docId": "131120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ":", "RB", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 177, "question": "When was the last time took, you know?", "question_tokens": ["When", "was", "the", "last", "time", "took", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 178, "answer": "As a matter of fact -- well, Alex has admitted that.", "answer_tokens": ["As", "a", "matter", "of", "fact", "--", "well", ",", "Alex", "has", "admitted", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 182, "question": "Alex Rodriguez says and you believe him that he's not taking performance-enhancing drugs for at least a decade?", "question_tokens": ["Alex", "Rodriguez", "says", "and", "you", "believe", "him", "that", "he", "'s", "not", "taking", "performance-enhancing", "drugs", "for", "at", "least", "a", "decade", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "JJS", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 183, "answer": "I absolutely believe him, because I've seen the evidence and it would defy science.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "absolutely", "believe", "him", ",", "because", "I", "'ve", "seen", "the", "evidence", "and", "it", "would", "defy", "science", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alex Rodriguez"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}, "docId": "131120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "What is your reaction to this latest incident involving your friend George Zimmerman, given it's now the fourth time I think that he's been involved in such a clash with the police?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "reaction", "to", "this", "latest", "incident", "involving", "your", "friend", "George", "Zimmerman", ",", "given", "it", "'s", "now", "the", "fourth", "time", "I", "think", "that", "he", "'s", "been", "involved", "in", "such", "a", "clash", "with", "the", "police", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "Well, Piers in my honest opinion and I'm not medical doctor, but I believed that George is suffering from untreated post traumatic stress disorder.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Piers", "in", "my", "honest", "opinion", "and", "I", "'m", "not", "medical", "doctor", ",", "but", "I", "believed", "that", "George", "is", "suffering", "from", "untreated", "post", "traumatic", "stress", "disorder", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "RB", "VBN", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 217, "question": "What?", "question_tokens": ["What", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 218, "answer": "... always been around ...", "answer_tokens": ["...", "always", "been", "around", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", ":"], "qSentId": 246, "question": "And someone knows slogan?", "question_tokens": ["And", "someone", "knows", "slogan", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "You know, you know, what ...", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "you", "know", ",", "what", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 275, "question": "You want to hear the facts?", "question_tokens": ["You", "want", "to", "hear", "the", "facts", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 276, "answer": "I'm just asking you this.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "just", "asking", "you", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", ":", "NNP", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "Is it say right to bear arm in it?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "say", "right", "to", "bear", "arm", "in", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "How many -- My point was you said as his friend, he's suffering from a mental illness, post traumatic stress disorder.", "answer_tokens": ["How", "many", "--", "My", "point", "was", "you", "said", "as", "his", "friend", ",", "he", "'s", "suffering", "from", "a", "mental", "illness", ",", "post", "traumatic", "stress", "disorder", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 319, "question": "He's on his way out to target and next thing you know, he's living his life on the run and he's got quite a few people after him, OK, because they believe that he murdered as you call it unarmed teenager, OK?", "question_tokens": ["He", "'s", "on", "his", "way", "out", "to", "target", "and", "next", "thing", "you", "know", ",", "he", "'s", "living", "his", "life", "on", "the", "run", "and", "he", "'s", "got", "quite", "a", "few", "people", "after", "him", ",", "OK", ",", "because", "they", "believe", "that", "he", "murdered", "as", "you", "call", "it", "unarmed", "teenager", ",", "OK", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJR", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 320, "answer": "He killed unarmed teenager.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "killed", "unarmed", "teenager", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "EX", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 332, "question": "Are you aware of that?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "aware", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "Well, I'm increasingly aware that there must be a correlation between his mental condition and his propensity to threaten women with guns, yes, because that seems to be a pattern with every woman that he comes across.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "increasingly", "aware", "that", "there", "must", "be", "a", "correlation", "between", "his", "mental", "condition", "and", "his", "propensity", "to", "threaten", "women", "with", "guns", ",", "yes", ",", "because", "that", "seems", "to", "be", "a", "pattern", "with", "every", "woman", "that", "he", "comes", "across", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Samantha"]}, "docId": "131120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", ",", "CC", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "I mean, what do you make of that?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "what", "do", "you", "make", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "Absolutely appalled, but Piers, I think there were some hints of what his possible defense maybe if as his prosecution proceeds involving the alleged victim Samantha, his girlfriend.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "appalled", ",", "but", "Piers", ",", "I", "think", "there", "were", "some", "hints", "of", "what", "his", "possible", "defense", "maybe", "if", "as", "his", "prosecution", "proceeds", "involving", "the", "alleged", "victim", "Samantha", ",", "his", "girlfriend", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "DT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 365, "question": "What about his wife?", "question_tokens": ["What", "about", "his", "wife", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 366, "answer": "... that would help the defense ...", "answer_tokens": ["...", "that", "would", "help", "the", "defense", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "IN", "JJS", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 370, "question": "Are they all opportunists?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "they", "all", "opportunists", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "Well -- but I mean according to his friend that appears to be the point of view that is at least his friend has.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "--", "but", "I", "mean", "according", "to", "his", "friend", "that", "appears", "to", "be", "the", "point", "of", "view", "that", "is", "at", "least", "his", "friend", "has", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "Does that worry you?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "that", "worry", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "That doesn't worry me.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "does", "n't", "worry", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "Are we now in a position where the Republicans would love Kathleen Sebelius to keep her job for as a long as humanly possible?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "we", "now", "in", "a", "position", "where", "the", "Republicans", "would", "love", "Kathleen", "Sebelius", "to", "keep", "her", "job", "for", "as", "a", "long", "as", "humanly", "possible", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "NNPS", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "NN", "IN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "Well, obviously many of us like myself warned about the problems we're seeing with ObamaCare and not just with the rollout but with the program itself.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "obviously", "many", "of", "us", "like", "myself", "warned", "about", "the", "problems", "we", "'re", "seeing", "with", "ObamaCare", "and", "not", "just", "with", "the", "rollout", "but", "with", "the", "program", "itself", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kathleen Sebelius"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "If somebody like you electable to the Republican Party as their nominee?", "question_tokens": ["If", "somebody", "like", "you", "electable", "to", "the", "Republican", "Party", "as", "their", "nominee", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "Oh, I think any of the 30 Republican Governors are and I think they prove it in the states.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "think", "any", "of", "the", "30", "Republican", "Governors", "are", "and", "I", "think", "they", "prove", "it", "in", "the", "states", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 500, "question": "What was your mind telling you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "mind", "telling", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 501, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "At what point did you realized what have actually happened and how did your parents deal with protecting you as the fact, you're so young?", "question_tokens": ["At", "what", "point", "did", "you", "realized", "what", "have", "actually", "happened", "and", "how", "did", "your", "parents", "deal", "with", "protecting", "you", "as", "the", "fact", ",", "you", "'re", "so", "young", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 513, "question": "Is there a day, Jeff Franzen, when you don't think about that day back in Dallas in '63?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "a", "day", ",", "Jeff", "Franzen", ",", "when", "you", "do", "n't", "think", "about", "that", "day", "back", "in", "Dallas", "in", "'63", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 514, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["'63"], "PERSON": ["Jeff Franzen"], "LOCATION": ["Dallas"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Vietnam"]}, "docId": "131120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ":", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "What was your conclusion?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "conclusion", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "Would've been very different, principally because I think based on the evidence, not wishful thinking, not some gassy (ph) hope that he probably would not have gone into Vietnam.", "answer_tokens": ["Would", "'ve", "been", "very", "different", ",", "principally", "because", "I", "think", "based", "on", "the", "evidence", ",", "not", "wishful", "thinking", ",", "not", "some", "gassy", "(", "ph", ")", "hope", "that", "he", "probably", "would", "not", "have", "gone", "into", "Vietnam", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 542, "question": "How would he have dealt with that as a serving president?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "he", "have", "dealt", "with", "that", "as", "a", "serving", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 543, "answer": "This was the darker side.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "was", "the", "darker", "side", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "-NONE-", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 560, "question": "Would you've been like Johnson, very proactive, or would've been a bit wary, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "'ve", "been", "like", "Johnson", ",", "very", "proactive", ",", "or", "would", "'ve", "been", "a", "bit", "wary", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 561, "answer": "I think it would be less (inaudible).", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "would", "be", "less", "(", "inaudible", ")", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Johnson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "CC", "WRB", "IN", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "RB", "RB", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", ":", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 568, "question": "Would he have become a truly great president, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "he", "have", "become", "a", "truly", "great", "president", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 569, "answer": "It's very hard to cut through what the death meant and how that put him in a different category, I think he would have been seen by historians as a reasonably successfully president and avoiding World War III gets -- that's a lot of points for me.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "very", "hard", "to", "cut", "through", "what", "the", "death", "meant", "and", "how", "that", "put", "him", "in", "a", "different", "category", ",", "I", "think", "he", "would", "have", "been", "seen", "by", "historians", "as", "a", "reasonably", "successfully", "president", "and", "avoiding", "World", "War", "III", "gets", "--", "that", "'s", "a", "lot", "of", "points", "for", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]